(Raj(running in):)Hey, guess what.
(Raj(running in):)I've been accepted as a test subject
for a drug...
(Raj(running in):)...to overcome pathological shyness.
- Oh, good for you, Raj.
- Yes, I'm very hopeful.
(Raj:)Hello, Missy.
(Raj:)They mentioned
there may be side effects.
(Leonard:)So, Missy...
(Raj:)...have you ever met a man
from the exotic subcontinent of India?
- Well, there's Dr. Patel at our church.
- Yes, Patel. Good man.
Do you like motorcycles?
Because I ride a hog.
A hog? You have a two-cylinder scooter
with a basket in the front.
(Howard:)You still have to wear a helmet.
- Have you ever heard of the Kama Sutra?
- The sex book.
(Raj:)The Indian sex book.
(Raj:)In other words, if you wonder, wonder
who wrote the book of love...
(Raj:)...it was us.